Yaroslov Horokhovets

Web && Blockchain Developer Sytova Street, Zaporizhzhia, Zaporizhia Oblast, Ukraine!

I am a web developer and systems specialist with a passion for Website development and software development.

My original discipline is Software Engineering, I completed a master's degree in Sustainable Engineering.

My work experience comprises 6 years of full-time engineering and application development for industrial and enterprise systems.

I have experience in programming and web and apps development. I can convert company requirements to functional

Experience

Django React Developer/ Mike, Canada.(Aug.2017 – April.2018)

- Developed Website the Backend of the website using Django.
- Developed the front-end of the website using React.js HTML CSS.
- CMS imeplment on site,
- Payment Gateway Integration

Full-Stack Developer / FortuneSoft, Singapore. (May.2018 – April.2019)

- Developed high performance customer web apps using React.js, Redux.
- Used React functional components and React Hooks.
- Used Tailwind-CSS framework.
- Maintained high-level expertise in React state management strategies, including Redux.

Python Django Developer/ Ajith Kumar, Qatar.(Set.2019 – Mar.2020)

- Developed Website, with a focus in Python Django development.
- Developed the front-end of the website using React.js + Material UI(or Styledcomponents, Tailwind CSS) + Typescript.
- Cloud computing platforms (AWS, Azure, Google Cloud),
- Managed services (Social API, Payment Gateway Integration)

SKILLS

- C, C++, Java
- PHP, Laravel, Codelgniter, CakePHP, WordPress
- Python, Django, Flask,
 Pandas, Numpy, Selenium,
 Beautiful Soup
- JavaScript, Jquery, React, Vue, Node, Express, TypeScript
- Solidity, Solana, Ethereum, Web3, Rust
- Flutter
- HTML, CSS, BootStrap
- Github, Gitlab, Bitbucket
- AWS, Azure, Goolge Cloud
- Social API(Google, Facebook, Twitter)
- MYSQL. MSSQL, MongoDB, PostgreSQL, SQLite, Orcale

Education

Zaporizhia National Technical University (Ukraine Zaporizhia 2012-2015)

- Software principles and practices
- computer science
- Software testing and maintenance
- Cloud computing
- Development

PHP Backend Developer / Philippe, Switzerland.

(April.2020 – June.2021)

- Used SCSS and SASS for writing CSS styles.
- Built the back-end side using Laravel, CI and WordPress.
- Developed custom API layer to handle all CRUD operations.
- Built extensive test coverage for all new features.
- Collaborated with colleagues from other countries under DevOps process.
- Intragrate Google APIs(Calendar, Map, recaptcha)

Full-Stack Blockchain Developer / UmeeSoft,

US.(June.2021 – Dec.2021)

- Developed dApps on the Ethereum blockchain, with a focus in Solidity smartcontract development.
- Used Hardhat/Ganache/Solidity stack, along with Web3.js integration and various javascript frameworks.
- Built the front-end for dApps using React.js + Material UI(including Emotion) + Typescript.
- Built the back-end for dApps using Node.js and Express.js)

Laravel Developer / Philippe, Switzerland. (Feb.2022 – April.2022)

- Laravel Composer package development.
- Integration with Google Calendar API.
- Built reusable code and libraries for future use.

Highlights

- Good chatting
- Effective work time
- Organizational capacity
- Operability and commitment
- Ability to motivate colleague and maintain good relations
- > Resistance to stress
- Good manners

Hobbies

Fishing and Mountain climbing - a great way to unwind, unwind and keep your mind sharp.

Info

- Birthday2000/20/20
- Address
- Druzhniy ave., 3 apt. 10
- > **Zip code**: 69032
- > github

https://github.com/yaroslavhorok